Department of Geography fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Department of Geography fonds
1964 - 1988
F-12
2.75 m of textual records
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
Department of Geography
The Department of Geography was established by the Board of Governors in 1965 as one of the original Departments in the Faculty of Arts. The Department was responsible, through its Head, for the promotion of research and the development and delivery of programs in the broad fields of Human and Physical Geography. In 1965, the Department consisted of five faculty members and offered six undergraduate courses in the areas of economic, social and physical geography. Subsequent additions to its degree program offerings were a M.A. and Ph.D. in 1966, a B.Sc. in Physical Geography in 1978 and M.Sc. in 1981. The latter two degrees were both through the Faculty of Science. In 1979, the Department had 21 faculty. Members of the Department have also been involved in interdisciplinary programs with other departments and faculties, including the Master of Natural Resource Management Program in Applied Science; the Canadian Studies Program in the Division of Interdisciplinary Studies; the Institute for Quaternary Research; and the Latin American Studies Program in the Faculty of Arts.
The Department was administered by a Chair and a number of standing committees. The Chair was the chief administrative officer, whose responsibilities included the management of the operational budget; faculty tenure, promotion and salary recommendations; teaching assignments; and representation of the Department to external bodies. The number and composition of departmental committees varied little over time. In a draft Constitution of 1969, there were nine standing committees: Undergraduate Studies, Graduate Studies, Library, Accommodation and Equipment, Budget, Appointments and Guest Lecturers, Salaries and Promotions, Cartographic Services, and Tenure. By 1990, the Resources Committee had replaced the former Accommodation and Equipment and Cartographic Services Committees; and the Departmental Tenure Committee had replaced the Salaries and Promotions Committee. Ad hoc committees, such as the Chairman's Search Committee, were also formed.
published
Full
Revised
Title of the fonds is based on the name of the body.
The fonds of the Department of Geography consists of records created and received in the course of the administration of the department and the carrying out of its functions of providing instruction and promoting research. The activities documented include policy and procedures development; the planning, initiation and administration of curriculum and programs; departmental and faculty meetings; faculty salary, appointment, promotion and tenure deliberations; departmental reviews; and the publication of journals and reports. The types of documents include meeting agenda, correspondence, course outlines and examinations, an external review, faculty files, memoranda, minutes of meetings, and reports.
The titles and arrangement of series were provided by the archivist.
Hayter, Roger; Hickin, Edward J.; Roberts, Michael C.; Hurst, Michael Eliot; Sagar, Brian; Cunningham, Allan B.; MacPherson, Archibald
The records were transferred in a number of accessions from the Department between the early 1980s and 1989.
Additional material has been accessioned but not yet processed as of September 2002 (7.67 m., 1965-1995). Please consult the archivist for information about using these materials; restrictions may apply. Further accruals are expected.
Consult the inventory of the Faculty of Arts fonds. Consult also the inventory to the Canadian Association of Geographers, Western Division fonds.
Some files may contain personal or confidential information. Access to these files may be restricted as required by law. Files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
File lists are available.
- Policies and procedures, 1967 - 1969; F-12-1; 2 cm of textual records
  published
  Series consists of records relating to Department policies and procedures, and includes a draft Constitution.
  - Policies and procedures, 1967 - 1968; F-12-1-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 12-1)
    Textual records
    Pending review
  - Constitution, 1969; F-12-1-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 12-1)
  - Statement of goals, 1967; F-12-1-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 12-1)
- Correspondence, 1966 - 1988; F-12-2; 9 cm of textual records
  Series consists of correspondence received and sent by the Department Chair. It includes memoranda and reports.
  Access to the subseries "Subject files" is restricted in accordance with Freedom on Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
  - Subject files, 1966 - 1980; F-12-2-1; 6 cm of textual records
    Access to the subseries “Subject files” is restricted in accordance with Freedom on Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
    - Bralone Field Centre - proposal, 1971; F-12-2-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 12-1)
    - Enrolment statistics, 1969 - 1973; F-12-2-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 12-1)
    - Five year teaching plan, 1973 - 1974; F-12-2-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 12-1)
    - Grading, 1967 - 1969; F-12-2-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 12-1)
    - Phase III construction, 1966 - 1971; F-12-2-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 12-1)
    - Phase IV plans and allocations, 1970 - 1971; F-12-2-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 12-1)
    - Teaching assistants, 1969 - 1976; F-12-2-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 12-1)
    - Teaching assistants, 1977 - 1980; F-12-2-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 12-1)
  - Printed materials and reports, 1969 - 1988; F-12-2-2; 2 cm of textual records
    - Reports, 1969 - 1972; F-12-2-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 12-1)
    - Transportation studies, F-12-2-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 12-1)
    - Undergraduate curriculum report, 1988; F-12-2-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 12-1)
- Faculty members, 1964 - 1984; F-12-3; 24 cm of textual records
  Series consists of files related to the appointment of faculty members. It includes correspondence, curricula vitae, memoranda and reports.
  Access to appointments files is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
  - Faculty lists, 1965 - 1967; F-12-3-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 12-1)
  - Faculty - A, 1973 - 1980; F-12-3-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 12-1)
  - Faculty - A, 1973 - 1979; F-12-3-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 12-1)
  - Faculty - A, 1971; F-12-3-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - A, 1971; F-12-3-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - A, 1973 - 1974; F-12-3-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - B, 1973 - 1983; F-12-3-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - B, 1974 - 1975; F-12-3-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - B, 1979 - 1980; F-12-3-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - B, 1974; F-12-3-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - C, 1974; F-12-3-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - C, 1971 - 1972; F-12-3-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - D, 1978 - 1980; F-12-3-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - D, 1967; F-12-3-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - E, 1965 - 1969; F-12-3-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - F, 1971; F-12-3-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - F, 1970 - 1977; F-12-3-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - F, 1964 - 1973; F-12-3-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - G, 1972; F-12-3-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - G, 1971 - 1973; F-12-3-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - H, 1977 - 1980; F-12-3-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - H, 1978 - 1979; F-12-3-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - H, 1973 - 1976; F-12-3-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - K, 1980; F-12-3-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - K, 1971 - 1973; F-12-3-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - K, 1971 - 1973; F-12-3-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - L, 1970; F-12-3-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - M, 1977; F-12-3-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - M, 1965 - 1970; F-12-3-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - M, 1973 - 1974; F-12-3-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - M, 1972 - 1973; F-12-3-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 12-2)
  - Faculty - M, 1971 - 1972; F-12-3-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 12-3)
  - Faculty - M, 1977 - 1980; F-12-3-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 12-3)
  - Faculty - O, 1972; F-12-3-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 12-3)
  - Faculty - O, 1964 - 1974; F-12-3-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 12-3)
  - Faculty - O, 1974 - 1976; F-12-3-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 12-3)
  - Faculty - P, 1977; F-12-3-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 12-3)
  - Faculty - P, 1969 - 1970; F-12-3-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 12-3)
  - Faculty - P, 1972 - 1976; F-12-3-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 12-3)
  - Faculty - P, 1976 - 1984; F-12-3-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 12-3)
  - Faculty - S, 1966 - 1970; F-12-3-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 12-3)
  - Faculty - S, 1974 - 1976; F-12-3-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 12-3)
  - Faculty - T, 1977; F-12-3-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 12-3)
  - Faculty - W, 1978 - 1979; F-12-3-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 12-3)
  - Faculty - W, 1972; F-12-3-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 12-3)
  - Faculty - W, 1975 - 1978; F-12-3-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 12-3)
  - Faculty - W, 1970; F-12-3-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 12-3)
  - Faculty - W, 1979 - 1980; F-12-3-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 12-3)
- Departmental committees, 1965 - 1976; F-12-4; 71 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the records of various departmental committees. It includes circulars, correspondence, minutes of meetings, and memoranda.
  The arrangement of this series was established by the archivist according to subject.
  Access to records in the subseries "Promotions and Tenure" is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information
  - Appointment and Guest Lecturers committee, 1971 - 1973; F-12-4-1; 3 cm of textual records
    - Appointment and guest lecturers, committee, 1971; F-12-4-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 12-3)
    - Appointment and guest lecturers, committee, 1972; F-12-4-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 12-3)
    - Guest lecturers - Canadian landscape series, 1972 - 1973; F-12-4-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 12-4)
    - Guest lecturers - Geography in the 70's series, 1972 - 1973; F-12-4-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 12-4)
  - Budget committee, 1971 - 1973; F-12-4-2; 2 cm of textual records
    - Budget committee, 1971 - 1972; F-12-4-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 12-4)
    - Budget committee, 1973; F-12-4-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 12-4)
  - Cartographic Services committee, 1967 - 1969; F-12-4-3; 1 cm of textual records
    - Cartography committee, 1967 - 1969; F-12-4-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 12-4)
  - Chairman's Search committee, 1971 - 1972; F-12-4-4; 1 cm of textual records
    - Chairman's search committee, 1971 - 1972; F-12-4-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 12-4)
  - Department Meetings, 1965 - 1974; F-12-4-5; 28 cm of textual records
    - Department meetings, 1965; F-12-4-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 12-4)
    - Department meetings, 1966; F-12-4-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 12-4)
    - Department meetings, 1967; F-12-4-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 12-4)
    - Department meetings, 1968; F-12-4-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 12-4)
    - Department meetings - agenda and minutes, 1969; F-12-4-5-0-5 (Archival box - standard 12-4)
    - Department meetings - supporting papers, 1969; F-12-4-5-0-6 (Archival box - standard 12-4)
    - Department meetings - supporting papers, 1969; F-12-4-5-0-7 (Archival box - standard 12-5)
    - Department meetings - agenda and minutes, 1970; F-12-4-5-0-8 (Archival box - standard 12-5)
      Open
    - Department meetings - supporting papers, 1970; F-12-4-5-0-9 (Archival box - standard 12-5)
    - Department meetings - supporting papers, 1970; F-12-4-5-0-10 (Archival box - standard 12-5)
    - Department meetings - supporting papers, 1970; F-12-4-5-0-11 (Archival box - standard 12-5)
    - Department meetings - agenda and minutes, 1971; F-12-4-5-0-12 (Archival box - standard 12-5)
    - Department meetings - supporting papers, 1971; F-12-4-5-0-13 (Archival box - standard 12-5)
    - Department meetings - supporting papers, 1971; F-12-4-5-0-14 (Archival box - standard 12-5)
    - Department meetings - supporting papers, 1971; F-12-4-5-0-15 (Archival box - standard 12-5)
    - Department meetings - supporting papers, 1971; F-12-4-5-0-16 (Archival box - standard 12-5)
    - Department meetings - agenda and minutes, 1972; F-12-4-5-0-17 (Archival box - standard 12-6)
      Restricted in part
    - Department meetings - supporting papers, 1972; F-12-4-5-0-18 (Archival box - standard 12-6)
    - Department meetings - supporting papers, 1972; F-12-4-5-0-19 (Archival box - standard 12-6)
    - Department meetings - supporting papers, 1972; F-12-4-5-0-20 (Archival box - standard 12-6)
    - Department meetings - agenda and minutes, 1973; F-12-4-5-0-21 (Archival box - standard 12-6)
    - Department meetings - supporting papers, 1973; F-12-4-5-0-22 (Archival box - standard 12-6)
    - Department meetings - agenda and minutes, 1974; F-12-4-5-0-23 (Archival box - standard 12-6)
    - Department meetings - supporting papers, 1974; F-12-4-5-0-24 (Archival box - standard 12-6)
  - Graduate Studies committee, 1968 - 1976; F-12-4-6; 10 cm of textual records
    - Graduate studies committee, 1968 - 1971; F-12-4-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 12-6)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1972; F-12-4-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 12-6)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1973; F-12-4-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 12-7)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1974; F-12-4-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 12-7)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1974; F-12-4-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 12-7)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1975; F-12-4-6-0-6 (Archival box - standard 12-7)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1975; F-12-4-6-0-7 (Archival box - standard 12-7)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1976; F-12-4-6-0-8 (Archival box - standard 12-7)
  - Promotions and Tenure committee, 1970 - 1971; F-12-4-7; 1 cm of textual records
    Access to records in the subseries "Promotions and Tenure" is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
    - Promotions and tenure committee, 1970 - 1971; F-12-4-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 12-7)
  - Resources committee, 1969 - 1974; F-12-4-8; 4 cm of textual records
    - Resources committee, 1969 - 1970; F-12-4-8-0-1 (Archival box - standard 12-7)
    - Resources committee, 1971 - 1972; F-12-4-8-0-2 (Archival box - standard 12-7)
    - Resources committee, 1973 - 1974; F-12-4-8-0-3 (Archival box - standard 12-7)
  - Salaries committee, 1971; F-12-4-9; 1 cm of textual records
    - Salaries committee, 1971; F-12-4-9-0-1 (Archival box - standard 12-7)
  - Undergraduate studies committee, 1968 - 1974; F-12-4-10; 21 cm of textual records
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1968 - 1969; F-12-4-10-0-1 (Archival box - standard 12-8)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1970; F-12-4-10-0-2 (Archival box - standard 12-8)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1971; F-12-4-10-0-3 (Archival box - standard 12-8)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1971; F-12-4-10-0-4 (Archival box - standard 12-8)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1971; F-12-4-10-0-5 (Archival box - standard 12-8)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1972; F-12-4-10-0-6 (Archival box - standard 12-8)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1972; F-12-4-10-0-7 (Archival box - standard 12-8)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1972; F-12-4-10-0-8 (Archival box - standard 12-8)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1972; F-12-4-10-0-9 (Archival box - standard 12-8)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1972; F-12-4-10-0-10 (Archival box - standard 12-9)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1973; F-12-4-10-0-11 (Archival box - standard 12-9)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1973; F-12-4-10-0-12 (Archival box - standard 12-9)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1973; F-12-4-10-0-13 (Archival box - standard 12-9)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1973; F-12-4-10-0-14 (Archival box - standard 12-9)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1974; F-12-4-10-0-15 (Archival box - standard 12-9)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1974; F-12-4-10-0-16 (Archival box - standard 12-9)
- Departmental reviews, 1969 - 1970; F-12-5; 1 cm of textual records
  Series consists of materials relating to a Departmental review committee. It includes correspondence, memoranda, and reports.
  - Department review committee, 1969 - 1970; F-12-5-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 12-9)
- Course outlines and exams, 1965 - 1987; F-12-6; 1.55 m of textual records
  Series consists of files of undergraduate course outlines and examinations.
  - Geography 001-3, 1971 - 1976; F-12-6-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 12-9)
  - Geography 101-3, 1965 - 1967; F-12-6-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 12-9)
  - Geography 101-3, 1968 - 1969; F-12-6-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 12-10)
  - Geography 101-3, 1970 - 1971; F-12-6-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 12-10)
  - Geography 101-3, 1972; F-12-6-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 12-10)
  - Geography 101-3, 1973 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 12-10)
  - Geography 111-3, 1973 - 1974; F-12-6-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 12-10)
  - Geography 111-3, 1975 - 1976; F-12-6-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 12-10)
  - Geography 111-3, 1977; F-12-6-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 12-10)
  - Geography 111-3, 1978 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 12-10)
  - Geography 111-3, 1979; F-12-6-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 12-10)
  - Geography 112-3, 1973 - 1976; F-12-6-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 12-10)
  - Geography 112-3, 1977; F-12-6-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 12-11)
  - Geography 112-3, 1978 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 12-11)
  - Geography 121-3, 1973 - 1975; F-12-6-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 12-11)
  - Geography 121-3, 1975 - 1977; F-12-6-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 12-11)
  - Geography 121-3, 1978 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 12-11)
  - Geography 141-3, 1973 - 1976; F-12-6-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 12-11)
  - Geography 141-3, 1977 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 12-11)
  - Geography 151-3, 1968 - 1971; F-12-6-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 12-11)
  - Geography 151-3, 1971; F-12-6-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 12-11)
  - Geography 151-3, 1972 - 1974; F-12-6-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 12-11)
  - Geography 161-3, 1966 - 1971; F-12-6-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 12-12)
  - Geography 161-3, 1971 - 1973; F-12-6-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 12-12)
  - Geography 162-3, 1966 - 1969; F-12-6-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 12-12)
  - Geography 162-3, 1970 - 1973; F-12-6-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 12-12)
  - Geography 201-, 1974 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 12-12)
  - Geography 211-, 1965 - 1968; F-12-6-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 12-12)
  - Geography 211-, 1969; F-12-6-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 12-12)
  - Geography 211-, 1970 - 1971; F-12-6-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 12-12)
  - Geography 211-, 1972 - 1973; F-12-6-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 12-12)
  - Geography 212-, 1974 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 12-12)
  - Geography 221-, 1966 - 1968; F-12-6-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 12-12)
  - Geography 221-, 1969; F-12-6-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 12-12)
  - Geography 221-, 1969; F-12-6-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 12-12)
  - Geography 221-, 1970; F-12-6-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 12-12)
  - Geography 221-, 1971; F-12-6-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 12-12)
  - Geography 222-, 1974 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 12-12)
  - Geography 241-, 1966 - 1970; F-12-6-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 12-13)
  - Geography 241-, 1971 - 1973; F-12-6-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 12-13)
  - Geography 242-, 1973 - 1977; F-12-6-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 12-13)
  - Geography 250-, 1974 - 1975; F-12-6-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 12-13)
  - Geography 250-, 1976; F-12-6-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 12-13)
  - Geography 250-, 1976 - 1977; F-12-6-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 12-13)
  - Geography 250-, 1978; F-12-6-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 12-14)
  - Geography 250-, 1979; F-12-6-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 12-14)
  - Geography 251-, 1974 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 12-14)
  - Geography 262-, 1974 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 12-14)
  - Geography 263-, 1973 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 12-14)
  - Geography 311-, 1966; F-12-6-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 12-14)
  - Geography 312-, 1966; F-12-6-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 12-14)
  - Geography 313-, 1968 - 1971; F-12-6-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 12-14)
  - Geography 313-, 1972 - 1973; F-12-6-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 12-14)
  - Geography 313-, 1974; F-12-6-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 12-14)
  - Geography 313-, 1975 - 1976; F-12-6-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 12-14)
  - Geography 313-, 1977 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 12-14)
  - Geography 314-, 1967 - 1970; F-12-6-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 12-15)
  - Geography 314-, 1971 - 1972; F-12-6-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 12-15)
  - Geography 314-, 1973 - 1974; F-12-6-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 12-15)
  - Geography 314-, 1975 - 1976; F-12-6-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 12-15)
  - Geography 314-, 1977; F-12-6-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 12-15)
  - Geography 314-, 1978 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 12-15)
  - Geography 315-, 1967 - 1971; F-12-6-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 12-15)
  - Geography 315-, 1972 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 12-15)
  - Geography 316-, 1968; F-12-6-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 12-15)
  - Geography 317-, 1973 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 12-15)
  - Geography 318-, 1974 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-67 (Archival box - standard 12-15)
  - Geography 321-, 1966; F-12-6-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 12-15)
  - Geography 322-, 1967 - 1974; F-12-6-0-0-69 (Archival box - standard 12-15)
  - Geography 322-, 1975 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-70 (Archival box - standard 12-16)
  - Geography 323-, 1967 - 1972; F-12-6-0-0-71 (Archival box - standard 12-16)
  - Geography 323-, 1975 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-72 (Archival box - standard 12-16)
  - Geography 324-, 1967 - 1973; F-12-6-0-0-73 (Archival box - standard 12-16)
  - Geography 324-, 1974 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-74 (Archival box - standard 12-16)
  - Geography 325-, 1968 - 1973; F-12-6-0-0-75 (Archival box - standard 12-16)
  - Geography 325-, 1971 - 1979; F-12-6-0-0-76 (Archival box - standard 12-16)
  - Geography 331-, 1966; F-12-6-0-0-77 (Archival box - standard 12-16)
  - Geography 341-, 1966; F-12-6-0-0-78 (Archival box - standard 12-16)